* [English](javascript: initLocalize(); Localize.setLanguage('en'))
* [Español](javascript: initLocalize(); Localize.setLanguage('es'))
* [Français](javascript: initLocalize(); Localize.setLanguage('fr'))
* [Deutsch](javascript: initLocalize(); Localize.setLanguage('de'))
* [日本語](javascript: initLocalize(); Localize.setLanguage('ja'))
* [한국어](javascript: initLocalize(); Localize.setLanguage('ko'))

==================================

Menu

Close

* **Quick Links:**

##### Search Made in Alabama

 Include News

Privacy Policy
==============

We want to be very clear: We prohibit commercial marketing of visitor information and the disclosure of personal information without prior consent of the visitor.  We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, such as an email address. We use your email address to respond appropriately. This may be to respond to you, to address issues you identify, to further improve our web site, or to forward email to another agency for appropriate action.

Web sites developed by the State of Alabama may use cookies to carry user information from one page to another. An example is a search criterion. This information is not stored on our server but on your workstation. We do not track this information on our server. The cookies we use are set to expire at the end of your browser session. This means that when you close your browser they are deleted.

Our server tracks statistical information (through the use of server logs and statistical software) to help agencies hosted on our servers analyze and monitor the use of their sites.

We collect and store only the following information about your visit:

* the name of the domain from which you access the Internet;
* the date and time you access our site;
* and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.

We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

Please refer to individual Alabama State Agency Web Sites for their Privacy Policies, which may differ from the one displayed here.

### Internet Security Statement

Security is the most critical segment of the State of Alabama network. The State of Alabama considers the security of our partners’ and citizens’ information critical. We handle online information with commitment to ensure a secure environment that can be trusted to fulfill all confidentiality requirements. Documented steps are taken to safeguard information according to established security standards and procedures and we continually assess the newest technology for protecting information.

Our server tracks statistical information (through the use of server logs and statistical software) to help agencies hosted on our servers analyze and monitor the use of their sites.

Sensitive information used in financial transactions, such as social security numbers, banking information and personal data is confidential. ISD is committed to ensuring our partners’ and citizens’ confidentiality through the use of state-of-the-art information security and the adoption of appropriate privacy policies and procedures.

Please refer to individual Alabama State Agency Web Sites for their Security Policies, which may differ from the one displayed here.

#### Stay connected to what's happening in Alabama now.

* Email\*
    
    Enter your **email address** to receive periodic updates on the evolution of business in Alabama.

Ready to start your company's next chapter in Alabama?
------------------------------------------------------

Alabama may be small in size, but its ability to accommodate businesses seeking success is vast. See why companies like Mercedes, Airbus, Hyundai, and Honda have decided to call Alabama home.

**Alabama Department Of Commerce**

401 Adams Avenue P.O. Box 304106 Montgomery, AL 36130-4106

**Toll Free** [800.248.0033](tel:800.248.0033)

**Media Inquiries** [334.242.0400](tel:334.242.0400)

**Email** [contact@madeinalabama.com](mailto:contact@madeinalabama.com)

Languages:

[English](javascript:Localize.setLanguage('en'))

[Español](javascript:Localize.setLanguage('es'))

[Français](javascript:Localize.setLanguage('fr'))

[Deutsch](javascript:Localize.setLanguage('de'))

[日本語](javascript:Localize.setLanguage('ja'))

[한국어](javascript:Localize.setLanguage('ko'))

© 2024 Alabama Department of Commerce. All Rights reserved. See our [**Privacy Policy**](https://www.madeinalabama.com/privacy-policy/).
